Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
Walter Dorwin Teague Papers
1898-1960
1950-1959
Teague, Walter Dorwin, 1883-1960
109.0 linear ft.
Papers of the American industrial designer; died 1960. Collection includes graphic designs, business files, correspondence, construction files, manuscripts, memorabilia, models, and published writings.
148700
Biographical History
Walter Dorwin Teague (1883-1960) was an American industrial designer and founder of Walter Dorwin Teague Associates. For more than eighty years, the company -- known today simply as "Teague" -- has designed everything from aircrafts to gas stations to cameras, in some cases maintaining a decades-long relationships with satisfied clients (their work for Boeing spanned sixty years and four aircraft models). Today, the company lists Hewlett Packard, Nike, Microsoft and other major corporations among their clients.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Walter Dorwin Teague Papers is divided into eight series.
Source material contains original and reproduced works of others — art, printing, and lettering.
Designs comprises posters, pamphlets, illustrations, advertisements, border designs, product and package designs, and architectural designs.
Files is subdivided into four sections: Ritter Company, Boeing, U.S. Air Force, and General. Because the collection has received minimal processing, the General section also contains material related to the three named companies; the researcher is advised to read the inventory carefully to ensure location of all relevant items. The Boeing material includes shop drawings at the end.
The bulk of Memorabilia consists of samples — fabric, hardware, paneling. Other items include metal models and equipment order catalogues.
Writings is subdivided into published material, much of which has been removed for separate cataloging, and typescripts. Most relates to Teague's books. It includes articles and speeches by Teague.
By far the largest segment of the collection, the U .S. Air Force Academy series, concerning the Colorado Springs complex built in the late 1950s, contains specifications, construction drawings, files, correspondence, and equipment design catalogues.
Miscellaneous material (a scrapbook of news clippings, a model cash register, a crude model of the DNA molecule) completes the collection.
Arrangement of the Collection
The collection has received minimal processing. It is in rough order by series and within each series is roughly alphabetical.
Separated Material
Some published items have been removed from the collection and transferred to Rare Books for cataloging. Please see the Writings section of the inventory below for more information.
Other Related Finding Aids
A finding aid for the microfilm collection is also available (hard copy only). Please contact the repository listed above for more information.
Subject and Genre Headings
Industrial Design; Teague, Walter Dorwin, 1883-; Industrial design -- United States.; Industrial designers -- United States.; Architectural drawings (visual works); Articles.; Clippings (information artifacts); Correspondence.; Manuscripts for publication.; Pamphlets.; Photographs.; Posters.; Sketches.; Industrial designers.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Care should be taken when handling the material, as much of the paper is fragile/brittle.
Acquisition Information
Majority, gift of Mrs. Walter Dorwin Teague (Ruth), 1965.
Inventory
- Source material - other artists
  - Magazines (Box 2)
    The American Bulletin, June 1916
    The National Gallery
    Four American Books
  - Les Arts, 1914 (Box 2)
  - Book: G.E. Pazaurek, Kunstglaser Der Gegenwart. Klinkhardt & Biermann in Leipzig (Box 2)
  - Book: Modern Glass by Guillaum Janneau (Box 2)
  - Book: Ensembles Mobiliers, Maurice Dufrene Vol. 2 (Box 2)
  - Objets Usuels, Presente Par Gerard Sandoz (Box 2)
  - Abbey, Edwin (Box 19)
  - Booth, Franklin (Box 20)
  - Burroughs, Byron (Box 20)
  - Clark, Walter Appleton (Box 20)
  - Cleland, T.M. (Box 20)
  - Craig, Frank (Box 20)
  - Fancher, Louis (Box 20)
  - Gibson, C.D. (Box 20)
  - Green, Elizabeth Shippen (Box 20)
  - Guerin, Jules (Box 20)
  - Morgan, Wallace (Box 20)
  - Parrish, Maxfield (Box 20)
  - Penfield, Posters and Magazine Covers (Box 20)
  - Pyle, Howard (Box 20)
  - Sterner, Albert (Box 20)
  - Thany (Box 20)
  - Whistler (Box 20)
- Designs
  - Graphic Designs
    - Animals - cattle, other livestock (Box 3)
    - Animals - domestic poultry, wild felines (Box 3)
    - Animals - dogs, cats, wild bird (Box 3)
    - Animals - elephants, deer, camels, giraffes (Box 3)
    - Animals, small - foxes, squirrels, rabbits, rats, fish, reptiles, insects (Box 3)
    - Architecture (Exterior), 2 folders (Box 3)
      See also Expositions and Salons and Windows
    - Architecture: Cities, Streets, Buildings (Box 3)
    - Artists, French (Box 4)
    - Babies (Box 4)
    - Bags (leather) (Box 4)
      See also Expositions and Salons
    - Bathrooms, See Furniture and Interiors; Expositions and Salons; Windows
    - Books (bindings and illustrations and decorations for), See Expositions and Salons
    - Boston Society of Printers (Box 4)
    - Cards, Foreign, Postal (Box 4)
    - Children (Box 4)
    - Chiswick Press Literary Almanac to 1874 (Box 4)
    - Clocks (Box 4)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Jewelry
    - Egypt (Box 4)
    - Expositions, HSE Rules and Regulations (Box 5)
      List of Exhibitors
      Rules and Regulations Governing the Design, Construction, and Equipment of
      Concessions and Exhibits, Texas Centennial Central
      A century of Progress International Exposition 1934 Great Lakes Exposition
      Compendium - Rules and Regulations: Fairs
      Directory of Exhibits, Association of Gas Appliance and Equipment Manufacturers
      Rules and Regulations for Exhibitors and Concessionaires, 1935
      New York World's Fair 1939, Inc.
      See also Writings: Miscellaneous: "Painting and Sculpture in the World of Tomorrow: Fair-Commissioned Mural Painting"
    - Expositions, misc. literature world convention dates (Box 5)
    - Exposition (Box 6)
    - Costumes (Box 6)
    - Curtains (Box 6)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Textiles
    - Dupas (Box 6)
    - Farm Scenes, Statues, Bridges, Horseshoes (Box 6)
    - Flowers (Box 6)
      See also Architecture - Exterior; Expositions and Salons; Textiles; Paintings
    - Fruits and Flowers (Box 6)
    - Furniture (Children's) (Box 6)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors
    - Furniture (Box 7)
    - Fashions (Box 7)
    - Fireplaces (Box 7)
      See also Furniture and Interiors; Expositions and Salons
    - Expositions and Salons No. 1 (Box 7)
    - Expositions and Salons No. 2 (Box 8)
    - Furniture and Interiors (Box 8)
    - Furniture and Interiors No. 3 (Box 8)
    - Glass (Box 8)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Table Accessories; Lighting Fixtures; Windows; Pottery
    - Glass - Perfume Bottles, Vases (Box 8)
    - Furniture and Interiors No. 1 (Box 8)
    - Grille (Box 9)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Lighting Fixtures; Hardware; Pottery; Steamships
    - Furniture and Interiors No. 4 (Box 9)
    - Pictures of place settings, dinnerware (Box 9)
    - Grolier Fine Printing (Box 9)
    - Grolier Fine Printing (Box 9)
    - Grolier - Fine Printing (Box 10)
    - Hardware (Box 10)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Grille; Shops
    - Animals - Horses, hunting scenes (Box 10)
    - Guild and authors league (Box 10)
    - Illustrations - Wash - Black & White - Pen & Ink (Box 10)
    - Animals - Wild Felines (Box 11)
    - French Interiors by T.A. Strange - Furniture, Decoration, 17th & 18th century (Box 11)
    - Horses (Box 11)
    - Housing (Box 11)
    - Accounting (Box 11)
    - Housing - magazine and newspaper clippings (Box 12)
    - Interiors (Box 12)
    - Jewelry (Box 12)
      See also Clocks; Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors
    - Indians, Eskimaux, Gypsies - Races (Box 12)
    - Kitchen (Box 12)
      See also Furniture and Interiors
    - Leonardo da Vinci - Head (Box 12)
    - Leyendecker (Box 12)
    - Lighting Fixtures (Box 13)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Grille; Glass; Pottery; Shops; Windows
    - Maps and 18th Century Ornaments
    - Martin, Charles (Box 13)
      Empty.
    - Marine (Box 13)
    - Men - old, musicians, laborers, business (Box 13)
    - Men - football, baseball, golf (Box 13)
    - Men of fashion (Box 13)
    - Men - fashions (Box 13)
    - Men - nude, includes original sketches, photographs (Box 13)
    - Men - portraits (Box 13)
    - Men - portraits of Lincoln (Box 13)
    - Military (Box 13)
    - Paintings and art, clippings (Van Dyck, Monet, etc.) from magazines, publications (Box 13)
    - Medallions (Box 14)
    - Pottery (Box 14)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Glass; Grille; Lighting Fixtures; Sculpture; Statuettes
    - Paintings (Box 14)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Flowers; Negros; Sculpture; Statuettes
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
      Kodak-Pathe negatives
      Peterson's Magazine March 1876
      Article about James Whistler
      Reproductions of Artwork by Manuel Robbe, N. Diaz
      Sunday Magazine - St. Louis Post-Dispatch January 25, 1931
      Picture of a boat cut out from New York Herald Tribune, Sunday September 18, 1927
      Article an murals from The Art Digest, 15th February 1931
      Latin text
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14)
      Brochure: The "Last" Stradivarius Cello
      Stack of invitation cards: Exhibition of Writing Books at the Art Centre from George E. Plimpton Collection
      Brochure: Catalogue of a selection of Rare & Choice Books, Bernard Halliday, Leicester
      Hand written notes listing book exhibits
      Notice about American Institute of Graphic Arts
      Brochure about penwork from across the world
      17-page handwritten paper about the printing press
      Handwritten letters
      "The Mystery of Golf," Houghton Mifflin Company, 1908
      "Voyage Autour de ma Chambre par Xavier de Maistre" Riverside Press
      "A Book of songs and sonnets selected from the poems of Thomas Bailey Aldrich"
      News-Letter of the American Institute of Graphic Arts, November 10, 1923
      "Wordsworth in a New Light"
      "The Symbol and the Saint"
      "William Bird Esq."
      Drawings, maps, printings
      "The Poems of Maria Lowell" Riverside Press
      "Life of Dante" Houghton Mifflin
      "The Friend She Found at Christmas" by Annie Payson Call
    - Modern Design (Box 14)
    - Modern Interiors, Exteriors, Furniture, Cities, Decorative Art, includes one original etching or print, artist unknown, of the facade of the Cathedral of the Holy Sepulchre in Jerusalem; 4 folders (Box 15)
    - Mountains, landscapes, gardens (Box 15)
    - Negros (Box 15)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Paintings; Statuettes; Sculpture
    - Oriental Designs - Rugs, carpets, pottery (Box 15)
    - Painting, articles on (Box 15)
    - Pompeiian Ornament (Box 15)
    - Prints, colored (Box 15)
    - Railroad # 1 (Box 16)
    - Railroad #2 (Box 16)
    - Railway stations (Box 16)
    - Religious (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Books (bindings, etc.); Sculpture
    - Restaurants (Box 16)
      See also Furniture and Interiors; Steamships
    - Rugs (Box 16)
    - [Cutout articles from a French magazine] (Box 16)
    - Sculpture (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Negros; Painting; Pottery; Religious; Statuettes
    - Statuettes (Figures and Paintings) (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Negros; Painting; Pottery; Sculpture
    - Shops (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Hardware; Lighting Fixtures; Textiles; Table Accessories
    - Silverware, Picture Frames, Tapestries (Box 16)
    - Stage Sets and Costume Designs: See also Expositions and Salons, Theater. (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Theater
    - Statuettes and Paintings (Animals (Box 16)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Painting; Pottery; Sculpture
    - Sport (Box 16)
    - Steamships (Box 17)
    - "Television" - a brochure by the Columbia Broadcasting System (Box 17)
    - Table and silverware (Box 17)
    - Trees (Box 17)
    - Table Accessories (Box 17)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Glass; Shops; Textiles
    - Teague Borders (Box 17)
    - J. Walter Thompson Borders (Box 17)
    - Telephone (Box 17)
    - Textiles (Box 17)
      See also Curtains; Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Table Accessories
    - Theatre (Box 17)
      See also Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Stage Sets and Costume Design
    - Tissue Print of Table and Lamps (Box 17)
    - Type (I) (Box 18)
    - Type Specimens (Box 18)
    - Type (II) (Box 18)
    - Type (III) (Box 19)
    - Type (IV) (Box 19)
    - Type Specimens (Box 19)
    - Windows (Box 19)
      See also Architecture (exterior); Expositions and Salons; Furniture and Interiors; Glass
    - Women - nudes (Box 7)
    - Women - Outdoor sports, old women, bridges, stenographers, occasional costumes (Box 8)
    - Women - poses (Box 8)
    - Teague Advertising, 2 folders (Box 21)
    - Teague Designs: Layout, Borders (Box 21)
    - Teague Illustrations (Box 21)
    - Teague Illustrations (Box 21)
    - Illustrations (Box 22)
      Art in Buttons pamphlet
      Scranton Lace Company brochures
      Mounted illustration
    - Teague Illustrations (Box 22)
    - Teague Pamphlets (Box 22)
    - Teague Pamphlets (Box 22)
  - Pamphlets
    - Teague Pamphlets, 3 folders (Box 23)
    - Four blank Nowell sketchbooks (Box 23)
  - General
    Companies represented here include Charles Antell ("Ant"), American Safety Razor, Banco de Ponce, Air Force Academy ("AFA"), Boeing, American Cyanamid, WTA, and others. Material is in no particular order.
    - Ant 22A - Stats (Box 24)
    - Ant 20 - Truck Decoration (Box 24)
    - Ant 21 - Super Lanolin Test (Box 24)
    - Richards, Charles M., General Correspondence (Box 24)
    - Ant15 - Search for and Study of Potential Packaging Material (Box 24)
    - Ant 5 - 5E - Tripod (Box 24)
    - Designs - Pencil Sketches (Box 24)
    - Vendors (Box 24)
    - All-Steel Equipment, Inc. (Box 24)
    - American Seating Company (Box 24)
    - Test Runs Multilith Plates (Box 24)
    - Banco de Ponce - 2 color presentation paste-ups (Box 24)
    - Coat rack 3500 NLR 4520100 (Box 24)
    - Shaver Survey manual - Walter Dorwin Teague Associates (Box 25)
    - Report for American Safety Razor Corporation (Box 25)
    - Lighter Action Survey (Box 25)
    - Sketches of shaving, brushes, etc (Box 25)
    - AMSR [American Safety Razor] (Box 25)
    - Random sketches, cutouts, blueprints, maps (Box 25)
    - Boeing 124 Original and Negs (Box 25)
    - Model 707 Route and Economic Study, Boeing Airline Company (Box 25)
    - Analysis of Comments, New York Mockup, May 1, 1956 to November 1, 1957; Sketches, handwritten notes (Box 25)
    - Prospectus Concerning the Anderson Books (Box 26)
    - Walter Dorwin Teague Associates "Dimensions" Newsletter (Box 26)
    - ACY Labels (Box 26)
    - ACY Labels (Box 26)
    - Company logos/labels (Box 26)
    - Foreign Letterheads (Box 26)
    - ACY - Job authorizations and correspondence (Box 26)
    - ACY 2H2 - Label Ref Manual (Box 26)
    - Aero Catalyst Manual (Box 26)
    - Heywood-Wakefield Company samples (Box 26)
    - Nehi soda boxes (Box 27)
    - Fastabs ads (Box 27)
    - Ant - Point of Purchase material (Box 27)
    - Ant 1 - Design Council (Box 27)
    - Ant 2 through 4B - Beauty Line, liquid makeup, Super lanolin, Charles Anteil (Box 27)
    - Ant 6 - Touch up, makeup comb. (Box 27)
    - Ant 7 - Super lanolin spray (Box 27)
    - Ant 10 - field survey of drug retailers (Box 27)
    - Ant 13 - Study of present CA production, shipping by storage conditions (Box 27)
    - Ant 14 - Study of competitive packaging (Box 27)
    - Ant 17 - Study of wholesaler and Rack jobber conditions (Box 27)
    - Ant 11 - Supermarket and Variety Store study (Box 27)
    - Ant 8 - Survey materials - drug stores (Box 27)
    - Ant 16 - Preparation of material for consumer survey by preference test (Box 27)
    - Ant 9 - TV film commercials material (Box 27)
    - Ant - Memos, Reports, Correspondence, Quotes, etc (Box 27)
    - Ant 19 - Design Studies (Box 27)
  - Specifications
    - Construction
      - Federal Specifications FF-R-556 - KK-L-31 la (Box 28)
      - Military Specifications (Box 28)
      - Federal Specifications MM-L-736 - OO-S-811 (Box 28)
      - Federal Specifications AA-S-71 - AA-W-128 (Box 28)
    - General
      - Federal Specifications L-U-671 - W-S-896A (Box 29)
      - Federal Specifications QQ-S-55 1 - QQ-S-00779 (Box 29)
      - Federal Specifications C-F-202 - L-T-775 (Box 29)
      - Federal Specifications QQ-A-245 - QQ-R-571a (Box 29)
      - Unlabeled (Box 30)
      - Federal Specifications RR-B-181 - TT-W-571c (Box 30)
      - Classification USAF S-1-1 Index of Federal Specs and Standards (Box 30)
      - Federal Specifications JAN-P-108 (Box 30)
      - Federal Specifications WW-C-566a - ZZ-T-301a (Box 31)
      - Federal Specifications AA-B-564 - AA-C-555 (Box 31)
      - Federal Specifications AA-D-97 - AA-R-111 (Box 31)
      - Federal Specifications LLL-A - PPP-V-205 (Box 31)
      - Specifications (Box 32)
      - Valet Unit - 3500NLR8830700 (Box 32)
      - Med Cab - 3500NLR8820800 (Box 32)
      - GSA Stores Stock Catalog (Box 32)
      - Binder - Com STDS (Box 32)
      - Index of Federal Specifications and Standards, General Services Administration Federal Supply Service, January 1, 1956 (Box 32)
      - Federal Specifications CC-M-636a - FF-N-836 (Box 32)
      - Specifications - Hagley Museum, Wilmington, Delaware, 4 copies (Box 33)
    - American Cyanamid Company
      - American Cyanamid Company (Box 33)
      - Packaging materials papers (Box 34)
      - B-Series Rubber Chemicals (Box 34)
      - Metal can specs (Box 34)
      - Container specification (Box 35)
    - Index of Federal Specifications and Standards, General Services Administration, Federal Supply Service, January 1, 1957 (Box 35)
    - Federal Specification Textile Test Methods - Walter Dorwin Teague Associates (Box 35)
- Files
  - Ritter Company
    - RD 17 (Box 36)
    - RD 16 - Audio Analgesic - Job began 10/14/59 (Box 36)
    - Golden Chair (Box 36)
    - 4.RD 15-CBP (Box 36)
    - RD 13 - Air Rotor Control Box Correspondence (Box 36)
    - RD 13 - Air Rotor Control Box Memos (Box 36)
    - RD 13 - Air Rotor Control Box Conference Reports (Box 36)
    - RD 13 - Air Rotor Control Box Drafts - Photos (Box 36)
    - RD 13 - Shipping & Rec. Tickets (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Correspondence with client (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Correspondence with others (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Conference Reports (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Memoranda (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Rough Note - Reports, Memos, etc. (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Proposals, Cost Estimates, & Contract (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Budget Reports (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Overall Specs, Schematics, and Cycles (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Calculations (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Component Specifications (Box 36)
    - RD 8 - Clients and Competitors Catalogues (Box 37)
    - RD 8 - Test Data and Test Instructions (Box 37)
    - RD 8 - Disclosures (Box 37)
    - RD 8 - Shipping and Receiving Tickets & PO (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Correspondence with Client (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Correspondence with Others (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Memos, Conference Reports (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Calculations (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Ritter Drawings (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Rough Notes and Sketches (Box 37)
    - RD 7 - Shipping and Rec. Tickets, Purchase Orders (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Correspondence with Client (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Conference Reports (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Correspondence with others (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Memoranda (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - WDTA Reports (formal) (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Rough Notes (Reports, memos, etc) (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Proposals, Cost Estimates, and Contracts (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Budget Reports (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Budget and Program Schedules (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Overall specs, schematics, and cycles (Box 37)
    - RD 6 - Calculations (Box 37)
    - RD 8 - Rough Notes and Sketches (Box 38)
    - RD 8 - Related Technical Data (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Component Specifications (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Rough Notes and Sketches (design) (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Related Technical Data (published info) (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Clients and Competitors Catalogues (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Test Data and Test Instructions (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Disclosures (Box 38)
    - RD 6 - Shipping and Receiving Tickets and P.O.s (Box 38)
    - Report No. RD-6-1 Ritter Company Surgery Table Phase 1 Engineering Report. June 22, 1956 (Box 38)
    - RD 5 - Correspondence with Client (Box 38)
    - RD 5 - Conference Reports (Box 38)
    - Industrial Design in US (Plaut) (Box 38)
  - Boeing
    - Soda labels (Box 39)
    - Boeing Office and Laboratory Facilities, Walter Dorwin Teague Associates (Box 39)
    - Estimates and miscellaneous (Box 39)
    - Washington, D.C. Marked Prints (Box 39)
    - South Park Site Development maps/blueprints (Box 39)
    - Boeing US (Box 39)
    - Report on Study and Evaluation of Proposed Site Plan and Orientation of Boeing Facilities on Glendale Site. November 18, 1958 (Box 39)
    - Furniture Pasteups, Catalogs, and Estimates (Box 39)
    - Boeing - BSRL Prints, shop drawings; 3 large envelopes (Box 40)
  - Air Force Academy
    - Emco Corporation Shop Drawings - 3rd, 4th, 5th submissions (Box 41)
    - Emco Corporation Shop Drawings - Approved by WDTA (Box 41)
    - USMA 2 - Emco (Box 41)
    - Emco Corporation Shop Drawings (Box 41)
    - Drexel Furniture Corporation (Box 41)
    - Blair - Shop Drawings (Box 42)
    - Max Blau and Sons (Box 42)
    - Bro-Dart Industries (Box 42)
    - Cal-Ohm Laboratories, Inc. (Box 42)
    - Blair Aluminum Furniture Company (Box 42)
    - Blair Aluminum Furniture Company (Box 42)
    - FA-2-A Shop Drawings (Box 43)
    - GFC Manufacturing Co., Inc (Box 43)
    - Emco Corp Shop Drawings (Box 43)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 44)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 45)
    - Harris-Hub Company (Box 45)
    - Shop Dwgs AFA 14/15 (57-13) Huntington Chair Corporation - Cabinet, Bookcases, Cabinets & Desk, Desk Components (Box 46)
    - Hermsdorf Fixture Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box 47)
    - Blair Aluminum Furniture Company (Box 48)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 48)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 48)
    - International Silver Company (Box 48)
    - Emeco Corporation (Box 49)
    - JG Furniture Company (Box 49)
    - Huntington Chair Corporation (Box 49)
    - Huntington Chair Corporation (Box 50)
    - JG Furniture Company (Box 51)
    - Laurel Lamp Manufacturing Co., Inc. (Box 51)
    - Ludwig & Patterson Co. (Box 52)
    - Robert E. McKee, General Contractor, Inc. (Box 52)
    - Metalab Equipment Company (Box 52)
    - Red Circle Display Case Company (Box 53)
    - Thonet Industries Inc. (Box 53)
    - Thonet Industries Inc (Box 53)
    - US Air Force Academy, Denver, CO (Box 53)
    - American Seating Company (Box 54)
    - Architectural Fixture Corp. (Box 54)
    - Architectural Metalcrafts Corp. (Box 54)
    - Blair Aluminum Furniture Co. (Box 55)
  - Ritter
    - Ritter 1. Ritter Company, Inc. (Box 56)
    - Ritter 1. Ritter Company, Inc. (Box 57)
    - Ritter (Box 58)
    - RD-5 Ritter Sterilizer - Computations, Data Prints, etc. (Box 58)